<<<<<<< HEAD
export const QuizArr = [
  {
    question: 'What comes after 1',
    options: ['2', '3', '4', '5'],
    answer: 0,
    points:2 // <- Index of answer array
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is Best In Javascript?',
    options: ['Vaishnavi', 'Adika', 'Bhavesh', 'Atharva'],
    answer: 2, 
    points:2 // <- Index of answer array
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is Best In CSS?',
    options: ['Vaishnavi', 'Atharva', 'Bhavesh', 'Adika'],
    answer: 1, 
    points:3 // <- Index of answer array
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is Best In Typescript?',
    options: ['Bhavesh', 'Vaishnavi', 'Adika', 'Atharva'],
    answer: 0, 
    points:3// <- Index of answer array
  },
  {
    question: 'Keyword used in Python to declare a function?',
    options: ['function', 'def', 'func', 'Def'],
    answer: 1,
    points:3  // <- Index of answer array
  },
];
=======
export const QuizArr = [
  {
    question: 'What comes after 1',
    options: ['2', '3', '4', '5'],
    answer: 0, // <- Index of answer array
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is Best In Javascript?',
    options: ['Vaishnavi', 'Adika', 'Bhavesh', 'Atharva'],
    answer: 2, // <- Index of answer array
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is Best In CSS?',
    options: ['Vaishnavi', 'Atharva', 'Bhavesh', 'Adika'],
    answer: 1, // <- Index of answer array
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is Best In Typescript?',
    options: ['Bhavesh', 'Vaishnavi', 'Adika', 'Atharva'],
    answer: 0, // <- Index of answer array
  },
  {
    question: 'Keyword used in Python to declare a function?',
    options: ['function', 'def', 'func', 'Def'],
    answer: 1, // <- Index of answer array
  },
];
>>>>>>> 411c27d13ff9f815d2713f08c6c8c6020398ec43
